lauramercier.com 2016-05-13

# eCommerce Solutions On-Demand | Demandware Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting [www.lauramercier.com](http://www.lauramercier.com/) (our "Site"). This Site is powered by Gurwitch Products, L.L.C. 

We appreciate the opportunity to interact with you on the Internet and are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, that information.

###### **What Information We Collect and How We Use It**

Any information we collect on our Site generally falls into the following two categories: Personally Identifiable Information or Aggregate Information.

###### **1\. Personally Identifiable Information**

This refers to information that lets us know who you are or things specifically about you.

**A. Visitors**  
You can browse our Site using the Visitor function without revealing any Personally Identifiable Information. If you want to register or place an order, you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number). In such event, we might maintain a record of your contact, including such Personally Identifiable Information, in a file specific to you. We use this information to provide better service in the event that you contact us again.

**B. Registration**  
When you register to shop online as a Customer, enjoying full access to the many products available on our Site, we will collect Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number). This Personally Identifiable Information is securely stored and may be accessed under Contact Information. You are assigned an identification number and select your own username and password-both are needed to enter the Site and to access your Contact Information.

**C. Ordering**  
When you place an order for products, we collect Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, contact and billing information, credit card, and other transaction information). We use this information to deliver your order, process payment, and to communicate with you about the status of your order. We may provide information necessary to the delivery of your order to our shipping partners that may include the type of products ordered.

**D. Credit Card Storage**  
Credit card information collected at registration or for shopping bag orders is used only to process payment for the transaction and, generally, is not retained on our Site.

**E. Surveys and Promotions**  
From time to time you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information to complete surveys and questionnaires or to participate in user polls. We use this information to improve our products. We may also use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide you newsletters and other marketing information that coincide with your preferences. You may customize your marketing preferences, or let us know if you do not wish to receive any promotional materials, by adjusting your Subscriptions & Email options on the Site or through a link provided in an email communication.

###### **2\. Aggregate Information**

This refers to information that does not, by itself, identify you as a specific individual. Such information would include the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the Web site that referred you to our Site, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web), your operating system and browser type, and any search terms that you enter on our Site. Our Web server aggregates this information in order to monitor the level of activity on our Site, evaluate its effectiveness, and improve the content of our Site in order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable experience.

We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate Information, provided that such information does not personally identify you. We do not correlate any Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Information that we collect on our Site. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will be protected like any other Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Statement.

###### **Sharing Your Information**

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be stored in our databases in the United States.

**General**  
We may share Personally Identifiable Information you provide online with other Gurwitch-related entities and/or trusted business partners with whom we collaborate, as well as those that provide services to our Site. Where we engage non-affiliated third-party agents or contractors, we require them also to observe the intent of this Privacy Statement.

From time to time, we may provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.

Should Gurwitch or its related entities merge with or be acquired by another business entity, or its respective assets be acquired, you should expect that we would share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information to companies assuming the role of serving you and other users of our Site.

**Your Choices**  
Your permission is always secured first. We will not use or share the Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Site in ways unrelated to the purpose for which you provided the information, including those described above, without providing you a choice whether to permit any such unrelated uses.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**  
We take reasonable measures to ensure that any Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our Site is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for its intended use. If you wish to update or otherwise correct Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us, you may edit your information online after completing registration, or contact us as described in the "Contact Us" section, below, and we will assist you.

**Protecting Your Information**  
We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable Information you provide online from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. We employ physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information.

It is your responsibility to safeguard the password you use to access our Site. We strongly encourage you to change your password regularly to prevent unauthorized access. Because your identification number, username and password are specific to you, you acknowledge sole responsibility for any and all use of our Site conducted with your identification number and password.

**Use of Cookies On This Site**  
A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer’s hard drive that allows a Web site to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences in order to tailor its operation to your needs, likes and dislikes. Cookies also enable an Internet retailer like us to keep track of a consumer’s electronic "shopping cart" before completing a purchase. Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your Web experience. Accepting a cookie does not provide us access to your computer or any Personally Identifiable Information about you, other than the information you choose to share. Other servers cannot read them, nor can they be used to deliver a virus.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust yours (Microsoft Internet Explorer, Firefox or Google Chrome) to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely. If you turn off cookies completely, there may be some Web site features that will not be available to you, and some Web pages may not display properly.

To support the personalized features of our Site (such as your country and language codes, electronic shopping cart, and other ordering and browsing functions) we must send a cookie to your computer’s hard drive and/or use cookie-based authentication to identify you as a registered Site user. We do not, however, use so-called "surveillance" cookies that track your activity elsewhere on the Web.

**Use of Active-X and JAVA Applets On This Site**  
Active-X programs and JAVA applets are executable programs that can be transferred to your computer’s hard drive to cause your computer to perform functions in connection with your visit to a Web site. Our Site does not transfer any Active-X programs or Java Applets to your computer’s hard drive.

**Use of Third-Party Media and Research Companies**  
Our Site may run limited third-party ads only for those Merchant and Services Partners with whom we link. In addition, we may use third-party media and research companies to place ads for us on other parties’ Web sites.

**Links To Other Web Sites**  
Links to third-party Web sites may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide additional shopping for various other goods and services through our Merchant and Services Partners. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.

**Children’s Privacy Protection**  
We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children and encourage parents to be an active participant in their child’s online activities. Our Site does not target and is not intended for children under the age of 18, and we will not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from them.

**Changes To This Statement**  
Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed. If any changes materially affect the use of Personally Identifiable Information previously provided to us, we will obtain your consent prior to the retroactive application of any material changes. By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to contact_us@lauramercier.com, or call 1-888-637-2437. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention.

Updated and effective May 2013.  
©2013 Gurwitch Products, L.L.C., U.S.A, all rights reserved.
